you know can I ask you about your
relationship with Cristiano and are you
annoyed by any things he's said in his
interview I didn't read the interview so
I'm okay with that uh as I said before
now his national team is Portugal and
suggested that you gave him a bit of a
cold shoulder in the dressing room on
Monday why you say that because they put
out footage the fa and it looked like
because there was no sound that you were
a bit crossword they put the sound after
did you did you hear with the sound okay
you have to do it because you know what
happened he's like in Portugal we have a
problem that I was watching one on one
of the channels that was talking about
that was called was bad for 45 minutes
all of a sudden they go in a break
National Team stand with us with the
sound the sound says that he's joking
with me and so they they come back they
said there was a joke and they cut there
and they said if you want to see again
just go back but if they go back they
will see that was a problem but if they
told if they tell the the really true if
they explain what was in that video
people will know but now people doesn't
know so as I said this is national team
Manchester United will be my focus after
the World Cup after the 18th of December
because that is the final and you have
no problem with it I have no problem
with anyone I do my job and uh and and
is everything One Time One manager said
to me everything that you can control is
yourself so I think everyone thinks the
same way you have to control yourself
give your best and that's it